jadaliyya.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Jadaliyya

Arab Studies Institute (ASI), which owns and operates the website **_www._**[ ** _Jadaliyya.com_**](http://www.jadaliyya.com/) (the "Site"), takes your privacy very seriously. This privacy policy is intended to inform you about the information that is collected from you when you visit the Site; how this information may be used and disclosed; how you can control the use and disclosure of your information; and how your information is protected.

**Scope**

This privacy policy applies only to the Site. This policy does not apply to information collected through any other website or to the practices of companies that Jadaliyya does not control. Please note that the Site may contain links to other websites. For example, if you click on an external link on the Site and link to another website, then this privacy policy will not apply to any information collected on that website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites, and we recommend that you read the privacy policies of each website that you visit.

**What information the Site collects**

**Information you provide directly to us:**

You are not required to provide information directly to us in order to view the Site. However, when you use certain Site functions, such as when you register for certain services or directly contact the Site, we may ask you to provide information, including:

  * contact information, such as name, email address, postal address, phone number, and mobile number;
  * username and password; and
  * correspondence you send to us.

**  
Information we collect from other sources:**

We may access information about you from third-party sources such as social networking sites. For example, if you access third-party social networking services (such as Facebook Connect or Twitter) through the Site, your username and connection lists for those services;

**How we use the information that we collect**

**Email Communications:**

We may use the information that we collect to send you e-mail communications, such as editorial updates, information about your account or changes to the Site, and promotional messages about our own or our marketing partners' products and services.

**Changes to the privacy policy**

We may update this privacy policy at any time to reflect changes in our practices and service offerings. If we modify this privacy policy, we will update the "Effective Date." We will notify you of any material changes in the way we treat your information by placing a prominent notice on our site or sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account.

_Effective Date: May 20, 2011_

> Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Suspendisse consectetur vestibulum justo et molestie. Morbi convallis ornare ultricies. Duis bibendum ultricies tristique. Mauris semper ipsum vitae ante mollis cursus. Donec ornare, ante id accumsan dapibus, felis nibh pretium felis, in malesuada felis lorem vitae nisl. In a molestie mi. Ut nec dolor at purus eleifend fringilla.
